# **Steven Seaman**

4001 Benbow Court • Antioch, CA 94531 • 925-784-7943 • <u>s.seaman32@yahoo.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/steven-seaman-1bb5b72a/

#### <u>Summery</u>

Productive Inventory Control Administrator working toward a career in Data Analytics and Data Science. With experience ranging from designing systems of production to advising customers. An effective problem solver engaging customers through creative thinking, strong communication skills, and tailored information. Excel at assessing problems and identifying questions that need to be asked.

#### **Relevant Skills**

- Power BI
- Salesforce
- Python
- SQL
- Excel
- PowerShell

### **Education & Certificates**

- Associate of Science in Business Marketing | Diablo Valley College | Pleasant Hill, CA | Fall
  2012
- Currently Enrolled in the IBM Data Science Professional Certificate
  - Currently enrolled in Applied Data Science Capstone
  - ➤ Machine Learning with Python
  - > Data Visualization with Python
  - > Data Analysis with Python
  - > Databases and SQL for Data Science
  - > Python for Data Science and Al
  - ➤ Data Science Methodology
  - > Open Source tools for Data Science
- Ethics and Law in Data Science Certification | Microsoft | September 2019
- Analytics Storytelling for Impact Certification | Microsoft | August 2019
- Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Power BI Certification | Microsoft | August 2019
- Introduction to Data Science Certification | Microsoft | July 2019
- Eleven units of Accounting from Diablo valley college

### **Professional Experience**

Bay Area Beverage Company Inventory Control Administrator

2018-Present

- Daily pick line counts
- Weekly count of keg cooler
- Daily breakage report

- Monthly count of pick lines, keg cooler, and back stock.
- Interpreting expiration codes to determine if product is out of code

### **Architectural Metal Services**

2014-2018

# **Procurement/Expediter**

Ordering an inventory of consumables such as:

- Grinding discs
- Fiber discs
- Sanding discs
- Non-woven discs
- Cutoff wheels
- Sanding belts
- Non-woven belts
- Welding wire
- Welding rod
- Lubricating oil
- Sawblades

## Fabrication and installation of metal railing:

- Reading CAD print outs
- Cutting
- Welding
- Grinding
- Bending
- Polishing
- Painting
- Delivery
- Installation

Pestec, Antioch CA Field Representative

2014-2015

- Inspection in and around buildings for pests.
- Determine causes for pests in or around building.
- Treatment and removal of pests from affected areas.
- Recommended steps to prevent or lower the chance of future pest problems.

Examples included, landscape changes, building repairs or modification, food storage, and hygiene.

• Recording of pests and location they were found.